Zhiyan,
go open the door.
An important guest is coming.
An important guest?
Who could it be at this late hour?
Secondary consort,
move aside.
How dare you, daughter of a criminal,
return to the mansion?
Yes,
now that the Prime Minister's Residence has fallen,
I have nowhere to go.
I can only come back to seek Your Highness's protection.
Fortunately, Your Highness, out of old affection,
did not make things difficult for me.
Is there anything you need from me?
I'm in a hurry to serve Your Highness.
No matter how carefully you dress up,
you can't win His Highness's affection.
I advise you not to waste your efforts.
Is that so?
How would you know if you don't try?
You're just a pawn
in his hands.
When Prime Minister Shen falls,
he'll just discard you like an old shoe.
I advise you not to waste your efforts.
Don't get angry.
Come on.
Sit.
But I don't think so.
Look,
I'm still the principal consort of Prince Rui.
We're both pawns.
You're just a useless pawn that can be discarded at any time.
As for me,
if I'm discarded improperly,
he will lose everything.
Shen Suhe,
you were indeed useful
to His Highness in the past.
But times have changed.
The Prime Minister's Residence has fallen.
You may not
even get a chance to serve.
You'd better leave the mansion.
Otherwise...
Otherwise what?
Otherwise I'll...
You...
What are you doing?
Look.
What a beautiful body.
It'd be a pity to ruin it.
How about
I sell you to a brothel?
You should fetch a good price.
Do you think
His Highness will pay a fortune
to redeem you?
How dare you!
My mother died of poisoning,
my father was wrongfully imprisoned,
and our entire family was ruined!
Now,
I just want to send
those who have harmed me
and my family to hell.
Ling Chuchu,
I dare.
Shen Suhe,
I didn't harm your family.
Look at you.
Don't worry.
Mu Jinghao cherishes you so much.
If I hurt you,
I won't be able to stay here.
Shen Suhe,
you're a madwoman.
Don't worry,
I won't let you stay here.
I'm waiting for you.
My Lady,
we're already
struggling here.
Why did you mess with Ling Chuchu?
Because we're in a tough situation,
we need to use this pawn.
Zhiyan,
grind the ink for me.
Ink?
Okay.
Miss,
it's not the time
to read this novel.
A love letter
from the prince on the border
from the frontier.
How's that?
Royal gossip.
Isn't it exciting?
Miss,
what are you going to do?
Now that I'm back to the mansion,
although the Second Prince dares not deal with me openly,
he may
take action against me secretly.
So,
I need to find a reason
to make him hesitate to hurt me.
Prince Yu,
you won't return to the capital anyway,
why not help me
get rid of those two?
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up!
Now,
take this script out,
Find the bookstores
and peddlers.
Within two days,
make sure this book is widely distributed.
At any cost.
Miss,
this is absolutely not acceptable.
If this book gets out,
what will happen to your reputation?
Reputation or life, which is more important?
Reputation
or my father's life,
my brother's life,
and the entire mansion's future?
I've heard that
Prince Yu
is a ruthless demon.
If he hears about this...
He's far away at the border.
He won't hear about these trivial matters.
Listen to me,
just go ahead and do it.
Moreover,
his shadow guard approached me for cooperation.
Even if he finds out one day,
Lou Xi can be used as a shield.
New novels.
Your business is good.
Help me sell more.
Okay.
Do you want to read novels?
Thank you.
Come on.
New book for free!
These few books.
Are they all given away?
Okay.
New book!
Thank you.
New story!
Are they all given away?
Thank you.
New novels.
These are the new stories.
Have you finished?
The last one.
Prince.
Prince's love letter to his capital beloved.
A love letter from a thousand miles away.
Good.
How dare you be so bold.
Prince.
have we been exposed?
You...
You're not like what the book said,
to be with Princess Consort of Rui...
How dare you!
Before it gets out,
collect all the books!
I'm afraid it's too late.
Almost everyone has a copy.
Shen Suhe,
what do you want?
What are you doing here?
The princess consort is asleep.
I'm not here for her,
but for you.
It's about to change seasons.
The mansion has bought some bedding for her.
You need to get them from the warehouse.
Now?
But it's already night.
I've told you.
It's up to you to go or not.
Don't say that our mansion
has mistreated your master.
I see.
I'll go with you.
Everything is inside.
Go in and get it.
Where is it?
Why are you locking the door?
Open it for me.
Rui'er
- Let me out! - Rui'er!
Open the door!
What a lucky guy!
Princess consort,
don't blame me.
You filthy bastard!
How dare you!
You're still awake?
What did you do to me?
You'll know when you wake up.
I was instigated by the secondary consort.
If you go to hell,
don't blame me.
Shen Suhe,
why are you here?
Why is it so quiet in the mansion?
Yeah.
Princess Consort of Rui,
what a beautiful woman!
Miss,
don't joke with me.
Remember,
You only have two hours.
Just leave her one breath.
Yes.
If it wasn't me,
you would have been choked to death.
That's not the case.
It's just that the drug took effect a little slowly.
I can hold on a little longer.
And
I just don't want to see blood
and ruin the plan.
What plan?
You're here so late,
do you need something from me?
Yes,
did you write this script?
It was a temporary measure.
I'll explain everything
to you later.
Since you're here,
could you do me a favor?
Alright,
you explain to me
about the novel first,
then I decide whether to help you.
Please.
Just help me.
I promise to explain it to you later.
Okay?
Let go of your hands first.
Promise me first.
Then...
Remember that you owe me an explanation.
I will.
Somebody, help!
There's a thief in the mansion!
Your Highness, something's wrong!
I just saw a shadow
sneaking into the mansion.
Where is he?
I saw him sneak into the room over there.
What's the noise?
In the middle of the night.
Is there a thief?
Princess Consort
You wait outside.
Without my order,
you are not allowed to enter.
Yes.
This...
What's going on?
If this gets out,
it will be bad for our reputation.
Your Highness.
I did nothing.
I'm innocent.
It must be Shen Suhe who did this.
Damn it.
Get up.
Explain to Your Highness.
Nothing happened between us.
Your Highness.
It's her.
It's the princess consort.
It's the princess consort who asked me to serve her.
Then
I was knocked out.
When I woke up, I was lying here.
Your Highness.
You must believe me.
I'm innocent.
It's Shen Suhe.
She set me up.
Get away.
Shen Suhe,
don't think I don't know
you're behind this.
Your Highness,
convicting someone requires evidence.
I'm warning you for the last time.
Stop playing these boring tricks.
Otherwise,
I can't guarantee
your father's safety in prison.
Your Highness.
I'm innocent.
If you still don't want to see me,
I'll keep kneeling here
until you forgive me.
Your Highness.
Please open the door and see me.
Miss.
You've been kneeling all night.
Take care of yourself.
Get away.
You useless thing.
If it weren't for you,
would I have to suffer such humiliation?
It's all my fault.
Please
to make up for my mistake.
You are just a lowly servant,
how can you make up for it?
Miss,
where did you get
this thing?
I found it when I went out shopping today.
This book has been all over the city.
Everyone is saying that
the princess consort in it
is the one in our mansion.
You are useful.
Now,
send it to the palace.
Make sure to give it to my aunt.
Yes.
Shen Suhe,
I don't believe
you can stay in the mansion this time.
Shen Suhe,
I want to see
how long you can hold on.
I'll stay here
as long as I live.
If you dare, just kill me.
Do you think I dare not?
You are a bad woman,
and you even disturbed my parents.
It's not too much to kill you.
I'm a bad woman?
What about your concubine?
You saw her
having an affair with another man.
Should she be killed too?
You!
What a large mansion!
What a high and mighty Prince!
Now, you've made such a big joke.
I wonder what people are saying about you.
Are they saying
you're weak and incompetent,
unable to discipline your wives and concubines,
or are they saying
you're tolerant and magnanimous,
allowing them to live in a sinful way under your nose?
Shut up!
Beat him!
Beat him until he begs for mercy!
His Majesty's oral edict!
Your Royal Highness,
what brings you here
today?
His Majesty's oral edict.
His Majesty heard that
Princess Consort of Rui has misconducted,
which damaged the royal family's reputation.
Therefore,
Princess Consort of Rui shall move out of the mansion immediately,
and go to Lingguo Temple to reflect on herself.
She can't leave without an imperial edict.
Princess Consort of Rui,
please.